{"data":[{"question":"Caffeine in coffee is relative harmless if people drink it moderately.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"in","b":"relative","c":"it","d":"moderately","answer":"2","explain":" - Relative-> relatively","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"SPSSX is a computer program designed specific for statistical analysis with a large amount of data.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"designed","b":"specific","c":"statistical","d":"with","answer":"2","explain":" - Specific-> specifically","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"New York City, which is one of the largest cities in the world, is larger than any other cities in the United States.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"cities","c":"larger","d":"cities","answer":"4","explain":" - Cities-> city","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Even though she hated the food,but her father forced her to eat it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Even though","b":"but","c":"forced","d":"to eat","answer":"2","explain":" - But->x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"This diamond necklace is worth. It is made of glass.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"diamond","b":"worth","c":"It","d":"made of","answer":"2","explain":" - Worth-> worthy","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"When you get burns, you should ease the pain with warmly water packs.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"burns","c":"should","d":"warmly","answer":"4","explain":" - Warmly-> warm","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"'The shop cross the road is where I bought the flowers from.' said Mary.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"cross the road","b":"where","c":"the flowers from","d":"said","answer":"1","explain":" - Cross the road-> along the road","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"It was really surprise that those children survived the fire that destroyed all the houses.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"It was really surprise","b":"those","c":"survived","d":"the","answer":"1","explain":" - It was really supprise -> it was really supprised","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Mary was afraid that the English teacher would be angry to her because she left her English exercise book at home.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was afraid","b":"would be angry","c":"to","d":"left","answer":"3","explain":" - To -> with","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"If you try to concentrate on one subject for too long, you might fed-up and not really learn anything.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"try to concentrate","b":"on","c":"for","d":"might fed-up","answer":"4","explain":" - Might fed-up-> might be fed-up","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"}]}